BU Records: Office of the President (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1845-1981, undated, Bulk: 1961-1981
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- External, 1936-1981, undated; 3
  - Right to Work (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 138, Folder 17)
  - Right to Work (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 138, Folder 18)
  - Right to Work (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 138, Folder 19)
  - Right to Work (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 138, Folder 20)
  - Right to Work, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Right to Work, 1977-1978 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Right to Work, 1979-1981 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Rio Grande Federation of Health Centers, Inc., 1979 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Robinson Independent School District, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1960-1968 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Rocketdyne, 1963-1973 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Rockhurst College, 1977 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Rominger Advertising Agency, 1974 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Rosen Heights Baptist Church, 1979 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Rotary Clubs, 1962-1980 (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Round-Up Showcase, 1967 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Royal Ambassadors, 1959-1972 (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - The R. W. Fair Foundation, 1966 (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - S Cross Reference Sheets, 1960-1977 (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - Saint Paul House, 1962 (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - Sam Rayburn Public Affairs Symposium, 1981 (Box 139, Folder 17)
  - San Jose State University, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 18)
  - San Marcos Baptist Academy, 1964-1981 (Box 139, Folder 19)
  - Schlitz Brewing Company, 1964 (Box 139, Folder 20)
  - School Administrators Association, 1961-1963 (Box 139, Folder 21)
  - Scott and White Hospital/Clinic, 1967-1972 (Box 139, Folder 22)
  - Scottish Rite, 1957-1965 (Box 139, Folder 23)
  - Scottish Rite (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Scottish Rite (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Scottish Rite (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Scottish Rite (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Scottish Rite, 1969 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Scottish Rite, 1970 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Scottish Rite, 1971 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Scottish Rite (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Scottish Rite (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Scottish Rite, 1973 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Scottish Rite, 1974 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Scottish Rite, 1975-1976 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Scottish Rite, 1977-1979 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Scottish Rite (1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Scottish Rite (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Sears Roebuck Foundation, 1969-1973 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Second Baptist Church, 1969-1973 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Defense, 1975-1977 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - Selective Service Board, 1964-1966 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Sells Estate, 1960-1965 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Sells Petroleum, 1959-1960 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Sells Petroleum, 1961-1968 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Seminary Extension, 1964 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Senate Bill 11, 1971 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Senate Nomination Committee, 1966 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Senian Gakuin University, 1968-1976 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - Sesquicentennial Baptist Jubilee, 1964 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Seventh and James Baptist Church, 1965-1967 (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - Shell Assists, 1960-1969 (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - Shell Assists, 1970-1975 (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - Shell Assists, 1976-1979 (Box 142, Folder 13)
  - Shell Oil Company, 1960-1970 (Box 142, Folder 14)
  - Sinclair Oil Corporation, 1961-1962 (Box 142, Folder 15)
  - Site Selection Committee [Mental Retardation Community Programs], 1966 (Box 142, Folder 16)
  - Slater Food Service, 1960-1970 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Smoking, 1966-1967 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - South Main Baptist Church, 1980 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - South Park Baptist Church, 1977 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - South Texas Children’s Home, 1965 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Southeast Texas Baptist Association, 1965 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Universities, 1960-1963 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Universities, 1964 (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Universities, 1965-1967 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Universities, 1968-1972 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Universities, 1973-1974 (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Universities, 1975-1976 (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Universities, 1977-1981 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Universities — Manual for the Institutional Self-Study Program of the Commission on Colleges, 1967 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Southern Baptist Colleges (SBC), 1963-1965 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Southern Baptist Convention (SBC), 1960-1966 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Southern Baptist Convention (SBC), 1967-1969 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Southern Baptist Convention (SBC), 1970-1978 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Southern Baptist Educator, 1963 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Southern Baptist Journal, 1980 (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Southern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1960-1961 (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Southern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1962 (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - Southern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1963 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Southern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1964-1965 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Southern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1968-1980 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1975 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Southern Methodist University, 1961-1980 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Southern Pacific Foundation, 1964-1975 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Southern Pacific Railroad, 1965-1975 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1959-1979 (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - Southern University Conference, 1961-1970 (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - Southern University Conference, 1977-1979 (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - Southern University Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - Southland Paper Mills, Inc., 1962-1974 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Southwest Alliance for Latin America, 1966 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Southwest Alliance for Latin America, 1967 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Southwest Athletic Conference, 1958-1959 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Southwest Athletic Conference, 1960 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Southwest Athletic Conference (1 of 2), 1961 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Southwest Athletic Conference (2 of 2), 1961 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - Southwest Athletic Conference (1 of 2), 1962 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Southwest Athletic Conference (2 of 2), 1962 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Southwest Athletic Conference, 1963-1966 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Southwest Athletic Conference, 1971-1977 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Southwest Athletic Trainers Association, 1963-1966 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Southwest Baptist College, 1963-1975 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - Southwest Center for Advanced Studies, 1967-1969 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - Southwest Educational Development Laboratory, 1966 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - Southwest Research Institute, 1962 (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - Southwest Texas State College, 1962 (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - Southwestern Bell Telephone Company, 1963-1973 (Box 147, Folder 11)
  - Southwestern Life Insurance Company, 1963-1970 (Box 147, Folder 12)
  - Southwestern University, 1978 (Box 147, Folder 13)
  - Speaker’s Committee of 100, 1970-1971 (Box 147, Folder 14)
  - Special Committee Observing Congressional Activity, 1975 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Special Committee on Proposed New State Law School, 1978 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Sports Illustrated, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - St. Edward’s University, 1965-1970 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - St. Mary’s University, 1972-1978 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Standard Oil Company, 1959-1972 (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - State Associations of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1970-1971 (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - State Bar Grievance Committee, 1964 (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - State Bar of Texas, 1958-1964 (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - State Bar of Texas, 1965-1973 (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - State Board of Education, 1963, undated (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - State Commission for the Blind, 1964-1967 (Box 148, Folder 12)
  - Stephen F. Austin University, 1977 (Box 148, Folder 13)
  - Stetson University, 1966-1981 (Box 148, Folder 14)
  - Stewardship Advisory Council, 1959 (Box 148, Folder 15)
  - Student Conference on National Affairs (SCONA), 1971-1976 (Box 148, Folder 16)
  - Summer Seminar on Academic Administration [at Texas A&M University], 1969-1975 (Box 148, Folder 17)
  - Sunday School Board, 1963-1979 (Box 148, Folder 18)
  - Superior Oil Company, 1969 (Box 148, Folder 19)
  - Supreme Lodge Knights of Pythias, 1977 (Box 148, Folder 20)
  - Symposium on Baptists in America Culture, 1970 (Box 148, Folder 21)
  - Syracuse University, 1961-1968 (Box 148, Folder 22)
  - T Cross Reference Sheets, 1962-1977 (Box 148, Folder 23)
  - Taylor Bedding Manufacturing Company, 1962 (Box 148, Folder 24)
  - Taylor Publishing Company, 1960-1967 (Box 148, Folder 25)
  - Tax Reform, 1969-1976 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Television, 1961-1962 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - “Tell It Like It Is”, 1969-1970 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Tenneco, Inc., 1968-1977 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Tennessee Gas Transmission Company, 1961-1963 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Texaco, Inc., 1961-1978 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Texans for America, 1959-1961 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Texas A&M University, 1963-1980 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Texas Act Council, 1980 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Texas Adult Probation Commission (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - Texas Adult Probation Commission (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - Texas Adult Probation Commission (1 of 3), 1978 (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Texas Adult Probation Commission (2 of 3), 1978 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Texas Adult Probation Commission (3 of 3), 1978 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Texas Adult Probation Commission — Minutes (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Texas Adult Probation Commission — Minutes (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Texas Adult Probation Commission (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Texas Adult Probation Commission (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Texas Alcohol Narcotics Education, Inc. (TANE), 1959-1976 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Texas Assembly, 1967 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Texas Association of Black personnel in Higher Education, 1975 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Texas Association of Music Schools, 1968 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Texas Association of School Boards, 1978 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Texas Association of Women Deans and Counselors, 1962-1975 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Texas Baptist Convention, 1959-1965 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Texas Baptist Crusade, 1961-1965 (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - Texas Baptist Faculty Retreat, 1961 (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - Texas Baptist Historical Society, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - Texas Baptist Memorial Sanitarium, 1961 (Box 151, Folder 11)
  - Texas Baptist SchoolsDLComparative Enrollment Summary, 1960-1962 (Box 151, Folder 12)
  - Texas Baptist School Administrators, 1960-1974 (Box 151, Folder 13)
  - Texas Baptist School Administrators, 1974-1978 (Box 151, Folder 14)
  - Texas Baptist Student Convention, 1964 (Box 151, Folder 15)
  - Texas Bill of Rights Foundation, 1964 (Box 151, Folder 16)
  - Texas Breakfast Club, 1977 (Box 151, Folder 17)
  - Texas Centennial Celebration, 1936 (Box 151, Folder 18)
  - Texas Christian University (TCU), 1959-1979 (Box 151, Folder 19)
  - Texas City High School, 1980 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Texas Civil Judicial Council, 1959-1960 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Texas Civil Judicial Council, 1961-1962 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Texas Civil Judicial Council, 1963-1964 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Texas Civil Judicial Council, 1965 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Texas Civil Judicial Council, 1966 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Texas Civil Judicial Council, 1967-1968 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Texas Civil Judicial Council, 1969-1970 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Texas Civil Judicial Council, 1971 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Texas Civil Judicial Council, 1972 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Texas Civil Judicial Council, 1973 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Texas Civil Judicial Council (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Texas Civil Judicial Council (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Texas Civil Judicial Council, 1975-1976 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Texas Judicial Council (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Texas Judicial Council (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Texas Judicial Council, 1978-1979 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Texas Judicial Council, 1980 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Texas College, 1980 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Texas College Survey, 1966 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Texas Commission on Higher Education, 1960-1965 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Texas Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics for Women, 1972-1975 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Texas Committee on Natural Resources, 1968-1969 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Texas Committee to Preserve Local Government, 1962 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - Texas Constitutional Revision Commission, 1973 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - Texas Council of Church-Related Colleges, 1963-1981 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - Texas Department of Community Affairs, 1979 (Box 154, Folder 13)
  - Texas Department of Health, 1964-1979 (Box 154, Folder 14)
  - Texas Department of Public Safety, 1964-1975 (Box 154, Folder 15)
  - Texas Eastern University, 1976 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Texas Education Agency, 1959-1964 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Texas Education Agency, 1965-1966 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Texas Education Agency, 1967-1969 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Texas Education Agency, 1970-1971 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Texas Education Agency, 1972 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Texas Education Agency (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Texas Education Agency (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Texas Education Agency (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Texas Education Agency, 1974-1975 (Box 155, Folder 10)
  - Texas Education Agency, 1976 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Texas Education Agency, 1977-1981 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.), 1960-1963 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.), 1964-1965 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.), 1966 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.) (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.) (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.), 1968 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.), 1969 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.), 1970 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.), 1971 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.), 1972 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.), 1973 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.), 1974 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.), 1975 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.), 1976 (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.), 1977 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.) (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.) (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.) (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Texas Foundation of Voluntarily Supported Colleges and Universities (T.F.V.S.C.U.) (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Texas Highway Department, 1963-1964 (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Texas Independent Fund (1 of 3), 1979-1981 (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - Texas Independent Fund (2 of 3), 1979-1981 (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - Texas Independent Fund (3 of 3), 1979-1981 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Texas Instruments Foundation, 1963-1979 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Texas Insurance and Annuity Association, 1960-1963 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Texas Intercollegiate Student Association, 1966-1971 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Texas Interscholastic League Foundation, 1963-1965 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - Texas Law Enforcement Foundation, 1959-1964 (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - Texas Law Enforcement and Youth Development Foundation, 1966 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - Texas Legislative Conference (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Texas Legislative Council, 1960-1961 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - Texas Legislation Service, 1964 (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - Texas Local Board No. 77, 1961 (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - Texas Lodge of Research, 1963 (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - Texas Manufacturers Association, 1961-1974 (Box 159, Folder 13)
  - Texas Medical Center, 1968 (Box 159, Folder 14)
  - Texas Methodist Student Movement, 1964-1966 (Box 159, Folder 15)
  - Texas National Life Insurance Company, 1969-1972 (Box 159, Folder 16)
  - Texas Parks and Wildlife Department, 1973 (Box 159, Folder 17)
  - Texas Partners of the Alliance with Peru, 1965-1970 (Box 159, Folder 18)
  - Texas Police Association, 1974 (Box 159, Folder 19)
  - Texas Private Colleges and Universities, 1967 (Box 159, Folder 20)
  - Texas Scottish Rite Hospital for Crippled Children, 1964-1968 (Box 159, Folder 21)
  - Texas Society of Professional Engineers, 1962-1967 (Box 159, Folder 22)
  - Texas State Historical Survey Committee, 1969 (Box 159, Folder 23)
  - Texas State Parks Board, 1963 (Box 159, Folder 24)
  - Texas State Teachers Association, 1961-1978 (Box 159, Folder 25)
  - Texas State Technical Institute (TSTI), 1972-1980 (Box 159, Folder 26)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. — Austin Project (1 of 4), 1967 (Box 159, Folder 27)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. — Austin Project (2 of 4), 1967 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. — Austin Project (3 of 4), 1967 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. — Austin Project (4 of 4), 1967 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. — Austin Project (1 of 8), 1968 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. — Austin Project (2 of 8), 1968 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. — Austin Project (3 of 8), 1968 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. — Austin Project (4 of 8), 1968 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. — Austin Project (5 of 8), 1968 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. — Austin Project (6 of 8), 1968 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. — Austin Project (7 of 8), 1968 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. — Austin Project (8 of 8), 1968 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. — Austin Project (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. — Austin Project (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (1 of 3), 1969 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (2 of 3), 1969 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (3 of 3), 1969 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (1 of 2), 1970 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (2 of 2), 1970 (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (1 of 3), 1977 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (2 of 3), 1977 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (3 of 3), 1977 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc., 1978 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (1 of 3), 1979 (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (2 of 3), 1979 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (3 of 3), 1979 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (1 of 3), 1980 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (2 of 3), 1980 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (3 of 3), 1980 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc., 1981 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Texas Power and Light Company, 1960-1975 (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - Texas Power and Light Company, 1976-1979 (Box 165, Folder 8)
  - Texas Tech University, 1960-1980 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Texas Textile Mills, 1965-1969 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Texas Utilities Company, 1979-1980 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Texas Utilities Company (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - Texas Utilities Company (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - Texans War on Drugs, 1979-1981 (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - Texas Water Conservation Association, 1965-1970 (Box 166, Folder 7)
  - Texas Water Conservation Association, 1971-1976 (Box 166, Folder 8)
  - Texas Wesleyan College, 1975-1979 (Box 166, Folder 9)
  - Theatre Communications Group, 1963 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Title IX, 1974-1975 (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Title IX, 1976-1979 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - Travelers Insurance Companies, 1967-1974 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - Trial de Nova, 1962 (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - Trinity Baptist Church, 1974-1976 (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - Trinity University, 1968-1980 (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - Tuition Equalizer Grant, 1965-1977 (Box 167, Folder 8)
  - Twenty-Eight Million Program Joint Committee, 1961 (Box 167, Folder 9)
  - U Cross-Reference Sheets, 1966-1977 (Box 167, Folder 10)
  - Union Baptist Association, 1967 (Box 167, Folder 11)
  - United Fund, 1959-1974 (Box 167, Folder 12)
  - United Nations, 1975 (Box 167, Folder 13)
  - United Service Organizations, Inc. (U.S.O.), 1968-1970 (Box 167, Folder 14)
  - United States Air Force Academy, 1962-1965 (Box 167, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Army, 1974-1976 (Box 167, Folder 16)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, 1964-1975 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Civil Service Commission, 1963-1971 (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Commission on Civil Rights, 1963-1974 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Department of Education, 1976-1980 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Department of the Interior, 1967 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Department of Justice, 1971-1973 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, 1976-1978 (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Marine Corps, 1963-1972 (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Military Academy, 1979 (Box 168, Folder 9)
  - United States National Student Association, 1968 (Box 168, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Naval Academy, 1967 (Box 168, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Steel Foundation, Inc., 1962-1977 (Box 168, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Treasury Department, 1951-1967 (Box 168, Folder 13)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1968 (Box 168, Folder 14)
  - United Student Aid Funds, 1962-1965 (Box 168, Folder 15)
  - United Student Aid Funds, 1966-1969 (Box 168, Folder 16)
  - United Way, 1975-1980 (Box 168, Folder 17)
  - University Administrators, 1975-1977 (Box 168, Folder 18)